[Strings]
header = "玩家造型"
spartan = "超級戰士"
covenant = "星盟精英"
subheader = "選擇您在進行多人遊戲時的角色造型。"
button_key = "&a-button 選取 &b-button取消"
callout_1 = "O   O   O   O   O   O   O   O   O   O   O\r\n  \r\nThe Spartan program was spearheaded by Dr. Halsey. Of all those involved in the program, only a handful survived. The remaining Spartan cybernetic soldiers were equipped with mark-six, Mjolnir battle-armor. Each suit is highly customizable. From color-scheme to emblems, each Spartan is free to prep his armor as he sees fit."
callout_2 = "O   O   O   O   O   O   O   O   O   O   O\r\n  \r\nWhen the Covenant hit, they hit hard. Low-level infantry backed up by plenty of Elites - the iron heart of the Covenant military. A single Elite can decimate a sqadron of Marines. It has yet to be seen how a group of these would fare against a squadron of Spartains."
