[Strings]
c03_2010_mr3 = "It blew right through us..."
c03_2020_mr4 = "50-cal, rockets...didn't do a thing."
c03_2030_mr4 = "Where's the rest of your Platoon\?"
c03_2040_jon = "Wasted, Sarge."
c03_2050_mr4 = "And we will be too, Sir, if we don't get the hell outta here!"
c03_2060_mr3 = "You hit, marine\?"
c03_2070_jon = "N-no, Sir."
c03_2080_mr3 = "Then listen up!"
c03_2090_jon = "The Chief is gonna jump in this tank, roll across the bridge, and blow up any inhuman son-of-a-bitch dumb enough to get between him and the Prophet of Regret!"
c03_2091_jon = "Pull yourself together, because you're going with him."
c03_2092_jon = "When I joined the Corps, we didn’t have any fancy-schmanzy tanks. We had sticks! Two sticks, and a rock for the whole platoon – and we had to share the rock!"
c03_2093_jon = "Buck-up, boy. You are one very lucky Marine!"
c03_2094_jon = "Usually the good Lord works in mysterious ways. But not today! This here is 66 tons of straight-up, HE-spewing dee-vine intervention!"
c03_2095_jon = "If God is love, then you can call me cupid!"
c03_2096_jon = "You had your chance to be afraid before you joined my beloved corps! But to guide you back to the true path, I brought this motivational device!"
c03_2097_jon = "Our big green style cannot be defeated!"
c03_2098_jon = "What about that Scarab\?"
c03_2100_mr4 = "We've all run the simulations - they're tough, but they ain't invincible."
c03_2110_jon = "Stay with the Master Chief. He'll know what to do."
c03_2120_jon = "Yes sir, Sergeant!"
c03_2130_mr4 = "Thanks for the tank. He never gets me anything."
c03_2140_cor = "Oh, I know what the ladies like."
c03_2150_jon = "That's right, you mothers! Run!"
x03_0010_jon = "Not if we can help it, Sergeant."
x03_0020_mir = "Extract the Chief, and return to In Amber Clad!"
x03_0030_mir = "Roger that."
x03_0040_jon = "Status\?"
x03_0050_lhd = "Sir, the Prophet is bugging-out. Request permission to engage!"
x03_0060_mir = "Negative, Commander..."
x03_0070_lhd = "I'll vector two heavies for star-side intercept."
x03_0080_lhd = "Ma'am! Slip-space rupture off the target's bow!"
x03_0090_nv1 = "It's going to jump! Inside the city!"
x03_0100_nv1 = "There's no time, Sir!"
x03_0110_mir = "Green-light. Green-light to engage!"
x03_0120_lhd = "Punch-it! Get us close! "
x03_0130_mir = "Ma'am, without a destination solution..."
x03_0140_nv1 = "We are not losing that ship!"
x03_0150_mir = "(irregular breaths)"
