[Strings]
header = "Easy"
easy = "Normal"
normal = "Heroic"
heroic = "Legendary"
legendary = "Your foes cower and fall before your unstoppable onslaught, yet final victory will leave you wanting more."
easy_description = "Hordes of aliens vie to destroy you, but nerves of steel and a quick trigger finger give you a solid chance to prevail."
normal_description = "Your enemies are as numerous as they are ferocious\; their attacks are devastating. Survival is not guaranteed."
heroic_description = "You face opponents who have never known defeat, who laugh in alien tongues at your efforts to survive. This is suicide."
legendary_description = "&a-button SELECT &b-button CANCEL"
difficulty_key = "Property of UNSC.\r\nEarly prototype model."
callout1 = "Shield structure based off of Hunter research."
callout2 = "UNSC standard issue field machete for jungle regions."
callout3 = "Grip has a thin gelatin layer similar Spartan armor."
callout4 = "Double thick reinforced edges to hinder structural warping."
callout5 = "Unique layered design self-sharpens with use."
callout6 = "Quad tier design absorbs shock from side impacts."
callout7 = "040668 032069 070891 091893 101494 110897"
callout8 = "Skull density prevents exit with std .40 caliber."
callout9 = "Science is still uncertain why Elites can pronounce the letter M."
callout10 = "CHOOSE DIFFICULTY"
