[Strings]
header = "난이도 선택"
easy = "쉬움"
normal = "보통"
heroic = "영웅"
legendary = "전설"
easy_description = "귀관의 거침없는 공격에 적군이 두려움에 떨고 있습니다. 하지만 최후의 승리를 차지하려면 아직 넘어야 할 고비가 많습니다."
normal_description = "대규모의 코버넌트 부대가 귀관을 노리고 있습니다. 귀관의 냉철함과 민첩한 사격 솜씨라면 충분히 극복해 낼 수 있을 것입니다."
heroic_description = "포악하고 강력한 적군이 수없이 몰려듭니다. 귀관의 생존을 보장할 수 없습니다."
legendary_description = "패배를 모르는 적군과 대치한 상태입니다. 귀관의 사투조차도 적에게는 웃음거리에 불과합니다. 목숨을 건 사투를 벌여야 합니다."
difficulty_key = "&a-button 선택 &b-button 취소"
callout1 = "Property of UNSC.\r\nEarly prototype model."
callout2 = "Shield structure based off of Hunter research."
callout3 = "UNSC standard issue field machete for jungle regions."
callout4 = "Grip has a thin gelatin layer similar Spartan armor."
callout5 = "Double thick reinforced edges to hinder structural warping."
callout6 = "Unique layered design self-sharpens with use."
callout7 = "Quad tier design absorbs shock from side impacts."
callout8 = "040668 032069 070891 091893 101494 110897"
callout9 = "Skull density prevents exit with std .40 caliber."
callout10 = "Science is still uncertain why Elites can pronounce the letter M."
